Preliminary Inventory of the Arnold Beichman papers,
Hoover Institution Archives
Arnold Beichman papers
1932-2006
91030
Hoover Institution Archives
112 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize (45.2 linear feet)
The papers are comprised of writings, correspondence, and research materials relating to Arnold Beichman's career as a political journalist and author. The collection contains numerous articles and columns published in, as well as drafts of several books written by Beichman. The research materials consist of articles, clippings, and other printed matter largely pertaining to communism, the Soviet Union, and politics in the United States and Great Britain.
Beichman, Arnold.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1991.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
American journalist and author.
1913 Born, New York City
1934 Received B.A. degree, Columbia University
1940s Editor,
1950s-1960s Freelance journalist, wrote for and other publications
1968 Author,
1972 Author,
1973 Awarded Ph.D. degree, Columbia University
1970s-1980s Taught at the University of Massachusetts, the University of British Columbia, the University of Calgary, and Georgetown University
1982 Research fellow and visiting scholar, Hoover Institution
1983 Author,
1984 Author,
1986-2010 Columnist and reviewer,
1991 Author,
2010 Died
Scope and Content of Collection
The papers are comprised of writings, correspondence, and research materials relating to Arnold Beichman's career as a political journalist and author. The collection contains numerous articles and columns published in The Washington Times, as well as drafts of several books written by Beichman. The research materials consist of articles, clippings, and other printed matter largely pertaining to communism, the Soviet Union, and politics in the United States and Great Britain.
There is a substantial correspondence series at the end of the collection; correspondence is also interspersed among the research materials. These letters include exchanges with a number of personalities associated with anti-communist politics in the United States and Great Britain.
The collection also contains photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions, intercepted by American intelligence agencies during the Venona program.
Communism--United States.; Communism.; Espionage, Russian.; Great Britain--Politics and government--20th century.; Soviet Union--Foreign relations--Treaties.; Soviet Union--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Foreign relations--Soviet Union.; United States--Politics and government--20th century.
- Research materials used in the writing of, 1986-1991 (Box 1)
- Correspondence with William F. Buckley, 1983-1988 (Box 2)
- Research materials used in the writing of, 1986-1991 (Box 2)
- Research materials used in the writing of, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
- Research materials used in the writing of, 1986-1991 (Box 4)
- Photocopies of Soviet publications relating to operations of the CIA in various countries, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
- Annual report of the Security Intelligence Review Committee of Canada, 1992 (Box 4)
- Correspondence with, or relating to, Jay Lovestone, 1968-1990 (Box 4)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions from the United States to the Soviet Union, intercepted by the United States Army Signal Intelligence Division as part of the Venona program, 1941-1943 (Box 5)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions from the United States and elsewhere to the Soviet Union, intercepted by American intelligence agencies as part of the Venona program, 1940-1947 (Box 6-8.)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions from the United States to the Soviet Union, intercepted by American intelligence agencies as part of the Venona program, 1941-1946 (Box 9-10.)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage messages intercepted by American or British intelligence agencies, 1934-1937 (Box 11-18.)
- 8 videocassettes (VHS) containing episodes of program, 1998 (Box 19)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions from the United States to the Soviet Union, intercepted by American intelligence agencies as part of the Venona program, 1941-1946 (Box 19)
- Thesis by Arnold Beichman, "The Conservative Research Department: How an Elite Subsystem within the British Conservative Party Participates in the Policy-Making Process,", 1973 (Box 20)
- Election observers' briefing books and serial issues relating to elections in Ukraine, 1998 (Box 20)
- 2 videotape cassettes (VHS) containing episodes of program, 1988 (Box 21)
- Correspondence and printed matter relating to controversies surrounding The Cold War program and to the history of the Cold War, 1988 (Box 21)
- Memoranda, printed matter, and miscellany, relating to broadcasting activities of Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty (8 folders), 1976-1988 (Box 21)
- Writings, correspondence, and printed matter relating to the history of the Cold War, 1986-1999 (Box 22)
- Writings and printed matter relating to Soviet naval forces in the Pacific Ocean, 1983-1988 (Box 23-24.)
- Thesis by John Selim Saloma III, "British Government and the Welfare State," 1961 (Box 25)
- Reading notes made by John Selim Saloma III on British and American politics, 1960-1961 (Box 25)
- Printed matter relating to a trip to the Soviet Union by Arnold Beichman, 1986 (Box 25)
- Article by Arnold Beichman, "Postmortem for a Defunct Ideology," 1994 (Box 25)
- Thesis by Arnold Beichman, "The Conservative Research Department: How an Elite Subsystem within the British Conservative Party Participates in the Policy-Making Process," 1973 (Box 25)
- Drafts of thesis by John Selima Saloma III, 1961 (Box 26)
- Notes relating to thesis by John Selima Saloma III, 1961 (Box 26)
- Clippings relating to British politics, 1964-1979 (Box 26)
- Drafts, correspondence, and notes relating to thesis by John Selima Saloma III, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
- Notes and articles on conservatism, 1973 (Box 28)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to British politics, 1972-1973 (Box 28)
- Reading notes made by John Selima Saloma III on British politics, 1960-1961 (Box 28)
- Clippings, printed matter, writings, and notes relating to the British Conservative Party, 1961-1973 (Box 29)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1957-2004 (Box 30)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to American foreign policy and British politics, 1948-1992 (Box 30)
- Articles and papers by Arnold Beichman, 1963-1994 (Box 31)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1963-2003 (Box 32)
- Correspondence, 1964 (Box 32)
- Clippings, printed matter, notes, and correspondence relating to British politics, 1957-1971 (Box 32)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1959-1992 (Box 33)
- Articles and notes relating to Norman Podhoretz, 1982 (Box 33)
- Clippings on South Africa, 1965 (Box 33)
- Articles on British politics, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
- Syllabus and reading list relating to a course taught by Arnold Beichman, 1966 (Box 34)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1959-1997 (Box 34)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to British and American politics, Taiwan, Indonesia, political philosophy, and the Cold War, 1956-2002 (Box 34)
- Notes and articles relating to British politics, 1946-1979 (Box 35)
- Article by Arnold Beichman, 1973 (Box 35)
- Notes and articles relating to Norman Podhoretz, 1982 (Box 35)
- Article by Arnold Beichman, 2001 (Box 36)
- Clippings on China and Taiwan, 2001 (Box 36)
- Clippings on Iran, 1997-2000 (Box 36)
- Tom Wolfe correspondence, 1999 (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous clippings and other printed matter relating to American, British, and world politics, 1950-2003 (Box 36)
- 1 videotape cassette (VHS) of an awards ceremony honoring R.V. Jones, 1993 (Box 36)
- Articles and notes relating to British politics, 1968-1976 (Box 37)
- Articles and speeches by Arnold Beichman, 1959-2003 (Box 38)
- Articles and correspondence relating to Quebec, 1999-2000 (Box 38)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1976-1984 (Box 39)
- Correspondence and articles on world politics, 1961-1979 (Box 39)
- Political journals, 1969-1978 (Box 39)
- Issues of, 1972-1976 (Box 40-42)
- Various political journals and articles from journals, 1973-1978 (Box 42)
- Articles and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1965-1984 (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous printed matter, 1967-1984 (Box 43)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1959-1997 (Box 44)
- Articles and notes on American politics and the Soviet Union, 1975-1998 (Box 44)
- Transcript of an interview conducted by Arnold Beichman with Reza Shah Pahlavi II, 1990 (Box 45)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1974-1981 (Box 45)
- Articles and printed matter relating to communism, the Middle East, and literature, 1984-2003 (Box 45)
- Bound volume of issues of, 1933-1934 (Box 46)
- Clippings, printed matter, and notes relating to terrorism, 1971-1977 (Box 47)
- Book-length manuscript by Arnold Beichman on world politics, 1961 (Box 47)
- Clippings and memoranda relating to the Scientific and Cultural Conference for World Peace ("Waldorf Conference"), 1949 (Box 47)
- Notes and research materials for class on leadership, 1967-1968 (Box 48)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1976-1991 (Box 48)
- Articles and printed matter relating to terrorism, 1974-1981 (Box 48)
- Book review by Arnold Beichman, 1974 (Box 49)
- Papers and other research materials for class on leadership, 1961-1968 (Box 49)
- Clippings and papers relating to terrorism, 1972-1980 (Box 49)
- William F. Buckley correspondence, 1961 (Box 50)
- Daniel Bell correspondence, 1979 (Box 50)
- Conference paper by Arnold Beichman, "Secretary-General Kissinger's Concert of Euramasia," 1976 (Box 50)
- Clippings, printed matter, and notes relating to terrorism, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
- Correspondence, clippings, and printed matter relating to the Freedom of Information Act and privacy, 1977-1983 (Box 51)
- Account by Arnold Beichman of his Middle East tour, 1962 (Box 51)
- Correspondence and clippings relating to the Voice of America, 1982 (Box 51)
- Articles and printed matter relating to Alexander Solzhenitsyn, 1975-1982 (Box 51)
- William F. Buckley, Jr., correspondence, l990-1991 (Box 52)
- Robert Conquest correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 52)
- Irving Louis Horowitz correspondence, 1991 (Box 52)
- Papers by Arnold Beichman, 1990 (Box 52)
- Lecture by Arnold Beichman, 1981 (Box 53)
- Clippings and notes relating to China, Henry Kissinger, Adolf Hitler, and the Holocaust, 1977-1981 (Box 53)
- Book reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1978 (Box 54)
- Clippings and notes relating to Max Eastman, Armand Hammer, and Vladimir Bukovsky, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
- Book reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1976-1978 (Box 55)
- Clippings and notes relating to Hannah Arendt, anti-Semitism, Joseph McCarthy, and other subjects, 1965-1981 (Box 55)
- Book reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1979-1981 (Box 56)
- Articles and paper by Arnold Beichman, 1987-1991 (Box 57)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to Mikhail Gorbachev and China, 1987 (Box 57)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1984-1994 (Box 58)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1983-1994 (Box 59)
- Clippings relating to Alger Hiss, 1992-1993 (Box 59)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1988-1993 (Box 60)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1964-2003 (Box 61)
- 1 videotape cassette (VHS) containing a recording of, 1999 (Box 61)
- Herman Wouk correspondence, 1992-2004 (Box 62)
- Summary of Venona files, 1998 (Box 62)
- Photographs of Arnold Beichman in Algeria, 1957 (Box 62)
- Articles and papers by Arnold Beichman, 1973-1992 (Box 62)
- Printed matter and CD-Rom relating to McDonald's operations in the Russian Federation, 1999 (Box 63)
- Copy of book by Arnold Beichman, 1993 (Box 64)
- Proofs of book by William F. Buckley,, 2000 (Box 64)
- Issues of the, 1995-1998 (Box 64)
- Miscellaneous political journals, 1987-1999 (Box 65)
- 3 monographs, including copy of book by Arnold Beichman, 1993 (Box 65)
- Summary of Venona files, 1989 (Box 66)
- Miscellaneous political journals, 1998-1999 (Box 66)
- Articles, declassified FBI documents, and notes relating to Henry A. Wallace, 1948-1998 (Box 66)
- Declassified FBI documents relating to Henry A. Wallace, 1947-1948 (Box 67)
- Summary of Venona files, 1989 (Box 67)
- Book reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1999-2000 (Box 68)
- Declassified FBI documents relating to Henry A. Wallace, 1946-1949 (Box 68)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, "Some Notes Towards a Theory of Anti-Leadership: Ambassador Adlai Stevenson and Senator Joseph McCarthy," 2003 (Box 69)
- Article and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1983-1986 (Box 69)
- Articles and printed matter relating to Henry A. Wallace, Boris Yeltsin, and the CIA, 1949-1997 (Box 69)
- Articles and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1951-1999 (Box 70)
- Correspondence and report relating to the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951 (Box 70)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1988-1993 (Box 71)
- Correspondence, declassified FBI document, and monograph relating to Viktor Kravchenko, 1944-1992 (Box 71)
- 11 computer disks containing drafts of Arnold Beichman's memoirs, 1993 (Box 72)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1990-1993 (Box 72)
- Clippings, papers, and printed matter relating to Yuri Andropov, 1982-1983 (Box 73)
- American Bar Association reports, 1980-1982 (Box 73)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, "The 'End of Ideology' in Africa: The New Beginning," 1973. Includes research materials (Box 74)
- Reviews of book by Arnold Beichman and Mikhail S. Bernstam, 1983 (Box 74)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1957-1989 (Box 75)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to the American and international labor movements, 1955-1962 (Box 75)
- Clippings, papers, and printed matter relating to national security and intelligence matters, 1955-1985 (Box 76)
- Articles, correspondence, notes, and printed matter relating to Columbia University and higher education, 1968-1974 (Box 76)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1980 (Box 77)
- Clippings, paper, and printed matter relating to national security and intelligence matters, 1978-1984 (Box 77)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, 1994 (Box 78)
- Articles, notes, and printed matter relating to the CIA, espionage, and national defense, 1978-1983 (Box 78)
- Correspondence and printed matter relating to Robert Hutchins and the Fund for the Republic, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 78)
- Articles and papers by Arnold Beichman, 1960-1994 (Box 79)
- Correspondence relating to Henry A. Wallace, 1943-1952 (Box 79)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to William J. Casey and intelligence matters, 1981-1984 (Box 79)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1956-1996 (Box 80)
- Correspondence, printed matter, and declassified FBI files relating to Henry A. Wallace, 1946-1995 (Box 80)
- Articles and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1975-2003 (Box 81)
- Photocopies of decoded Soviet espionage transmissions from the United States to the Soviet Union, intercepted by American intelligence agencies as part of the Venona program, 1943-1944 (Box 81)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to the Cold War, Alger Hiss, and the Communist Party USA, 1988-1996 (Box 81)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1943-2002 (Box 82)
- Articles relating to student protests at Columbia University, 1932 (Box 82)
- Correspondence and notes relating to Arnold Beichman's book, 1983 (Box 83)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to American foreign policy and the American labor movement, 1974-1978 (Box 83)
- Herman Wouk correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 84)
- Correspondence, articles, and notes relating to Herman Wouk, 1947-1984 (Box 84)
- Notes, clippings, and printed matter relating to Herman Wouk, 1948-1981 (Box 85)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, "The AFL-CIO and Its Critics," 1984 (Box 86)
- Correspondence, clippings, and printed matter relating to Accuracy in Academia, Inc., 1985 (Box 86)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to Valentin Chernenko and the Soviet Union, 1983-1984 (Box 86)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, "Marxism: The Communism of the 1980s," 1985 (Box 87)
- Articles and printed matter relating to Marxism, 1969-1982 (Box 87)
- Articles and printed matter relating to the American and international labor movements, 1939-1974 (Box 87)
- Articles, notes, and printed matter relating to Marxism, 1982-1983 (Box 88)
- Syllabus and course materials relating to a class on American labor taught by Arnold Beichman, 1974 (Box 88)
- Papers by Arnold Beichman on Marxism, 1980-1982 (Box 89)
- Articles and printed matter relating to Marxism, 1983-1985 (Box 89)
- Papers, clippings, and printed matter relating to the American labor movement, 1960-1974 (Box 89)
- Articles and pamphlet by Arnold Beichman, 1962-1986 (Box 90)
- Articles and printed matter relating to the International Labor Organization and the American labor movement, 1953-1974 (Box 90)
- Paper by Arnold Beichman, "Marxism: The Communism of the 1980s," 1985 (Box 91)
- Articles, papers, and printed matter relating to Marxism, 1960-1985 (Box 91)
- Sources for quotations, 1960-1971 (Box 92)
- Transcripts and press releases relating to Pierre Elliott Trudeau, 1970 (Box 92)
- Reading notes, 1960-1972 (Box 92)
- Correspondence and reviews relating to Arnold Beichman's book, 1972 (Box 93)
- Reading notes, 1960-1972 (Box 93)
- Article by Arnold Beichman, 1967 (Box 94)
- Reviews of Arnold Beichman's book, 1972 (Box 94)
- Articles and printed matter relating to American and world politics, 1955-1971 (Box 94)
- Articles and printed matter relating to intellectuals and the New Left, 1962-1967 (Box 95)
- Notes on American culture and society, 1971 (Box 95)
- Articles, correspondence, and papers relating to British politics, 1974-1977 (Box 96)
- Michael Fraser correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 96)
- 6 compact sound cassettes containing recordings relating to Arnold Beichman's book, 1981-1982 (Box 96)
- Articles and speeches by Arnold Beichman, 1972-1986 (Box 97)
- Articles relating to fascism, 1969-1982 (Box 97)
- Articles and notes relating to Frantz Fanon, 1962-1973 (Box 97)
- Correspondence and articles relating to the British Conservative Party, 1978-1979 (Box 97)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1966-1975 (Box 98)
- Articles, papers, and notes relating to liberalism, 1955-1988 (Box 98)
- Articles and notes relating to modern politics, 1954-1975 (Box 98)
- Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1979-1984 (Box 99)
- Articles, notes, and paper relating to conservatism, 1969-1981 (Box 99)
- Articles, correspondence and printed matter relating to British politics, 1966-1981 (Box 99)
- Articles, notes, and printed matter relating to terrorism, 1968-1982 (Box 99)
- Articles, pamphlet, and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1982-1985 (Box 100)
- Articles and notes relating to Kathy Boudin, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
- Articles, reviews, and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1979-1984 (Box 101)
- Curriculum vitae, 1979 (Box 101)
- Correspondence relating to a projected book of memoirs by Arnold Beichman, 1968-1994 (Box 102)
- Articles and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1982-1984 (Box 102)
- Articles relating to a projected book of memoirs by Arnold Beichman, 1994-1994 (Box 103)
- Articles, papers, and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1974-1994 (Box 103)
- Interview with Arnold Beichman, 1993 (Box 103)
- Articles and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1983-1988 (Box 104)
- Articles and printed matter relating to a projected book of memoirs by Arnold Beichman, 1937-1994 (Box 104)
- Articles and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1984-1988 (Box 105)
- Articles and correspondence relating to Milton Friedman, 1987-1989 (Box 105)
- Articles, papers, and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1987-1994 (Box 106)
- Articles relating to Soviet disinformation and espionage, 1983-1984 (Box 106)
- Articles, paper, reviews, and speech by Arnold Beichman, 1957-1991 (Box 107)
- Articles and correspondence relating to Sovietology, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Articles and printed matter relating to Korean Air Lines Flight 007, 1983 (Box 107)
- Articles, paper, and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1981-1995 (Box 108)
- Lecture notes, 1974-1981 (Box 108)
- Transcript of an appearance by Arnold Beichman on the television program, 1972 (Box 109)
- Articles, paper, and reviews by Arnold Beichman, 1982-1995 (Box 109)
- Articles and notes relating to a proposed book of memoirs by Arnold Beichman, 1969-1979 (Box 109)
- Correspondence, 1935-2006 (Box 110-113)
  - Abrams, Elliott, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 110: 1)
  - Abrams, Rachel, 1994 (Box-folder 110: 2)
  - Adelman, Kenneth, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 3)
  - Amiel, Barbara, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 110: 4)
  - Barrett, Will, 1959 (Box-folder 110: 5)
  - Bartley, Robert L., 1985-1990 (Box-folder 110: 6)
  - Barzun, Jacques, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 110: 7)
  - Beazell, William, 1946 (Box-folder 110: 8)
  - Becu, Omer, 1953 (Box-folder 110: 9)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1975-1995 (Box-folder 110: 10)
  - Besançon, Alain, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 110: 11)
  - Blake, Patricia ( magazine), 1983 (Box-folder 110: 12)
  - Blum, Ron ( magazine), 1984 (Box-folder 110: 13)
  - Borchgrave, Arnaud de, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 110: 14)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1990 (Box-folder 110: 15)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1975-1997 (Box-folder 110: 16)
  - Bugli, Ralph, 1991 (Box-folder 110: 17)
  - Bush, Keith (Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty), 1990 (Box-folder 110: 18)
  - Carmichael, Joel, 1993 (Box-folder 110: 19)
  - Conquest, Robert, 1986 (Box-folder 110: 20)
  - Crankshaw, Edward, 1961 (Box-folder 110: 21)
  - Cranston, Maurice, 1993 (Box-folder 110: 22)
  - Crozier, Brian, 1994 (Box-folder 110: 23)
  - Decter, Midge, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 110: 24)
  - Dooley, Meg ( magazine), 1991 (Box-folder 110: 25)
  - Draper, Theodore, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 26)
  - Erlanger, Steven, 1992 (Box-folder 110: 27)
  - Edel, Leon, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 110: 28)
  - Edelstein, Julius, 1990 (Box-folder 110: 29)
  - Elegant, Robert, 1991 (Box-folder 110: 30)
  - F.[?], Charles F., undated (Box-folder 110: 31)
  - Feaver, George, 1976 (Box-folder 110: 32)
  - Feulner, Ed, 1983 (Box-folder 110: 33)
  - Feuer, Lewis, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 110: 34)
  - Fox, John, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 35)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 110: 36)
  - Frum, David, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 110: 37)
  - Gates, Robert M., 1992 (Box-folder 110: 38)
  - Gavin, John, 1984 (Box-folder 110: 39)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1968 (Box-folder 110: 40)
  - Glazer, Nathan, 1976 (Box-folder 110: 41)
  - Godson, Joe, 1953 (Box-folder 110: 42)
  - Godson, Roy, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 110: 43)
  - Godwin, Ronald S., 1990 (Box-folder 110: 44)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1983 (Box-folder 110: 45)
  - Golino, Carlo, 1973 (Box-folder 110: 46)
  - Goodman, Geoffrey, 1976 (Box-folder 110: 47)
  - Harries, Owen, 1991 (Box-folder 110: 48)
  - Heldering, Jerome, 1955-1992 (Box-folder 110: 49)
  - Henninger, Dan, 1991 (Box-folder 110: 50)
  - Hofstadter, Richard, 1969 (Box-folder 110: 51)
  - Hollander, Paul, 1983 (Box-folder 110: 52)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1952-1988 (Box-folder 110: 53)
  - Horn, Alan, 1957 (Box-folder 110: 54)
  - Horowitz, Irving, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 110: 55)
  - Huntington, Samuel, 1974 (Box-folder 110: 56)
  - Isaac, Rael, 1984 (Box-folder 110: 57)
  - Janeway, Eliot, 1975 (Box-folder 110: 58)
  - Janson, Charles, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 110: 59)
  - Kagan, Donald, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 110: 60)